[Music]
increasingly
foreign
[Music]
are responsible maintaining
foreign
[Music]
this course provides an or give an
introduction to the field of artificial
intelligence
artificial intelligence
of rational behavior intelligent
the emphasis will be on understanding
the fundamental concept
of focus emphasis on fundamental
knowledge of methods of blind as well as
informed search and ability to
practically apply the corresponding
techniques
multiplication methods and they can
knowledge of methods of blind as well as
informed search
yeah matters
area
representation planning and learning
robotics
um
[Music]
foreign
oh
let me switch to urdu as we have some
students who can't understand push
though so that is why
i will uh talk either in urdu or in
english
so the books which i am recommending to
you guys
for study they are here you know i i i
have mentioned
three three books here um
artificial intelligence by start russell
and peter norwegian
books for following
[Music]
foreign
which acts directing its activity
towards achieving goals
appreciated
[Music]
is trying to search amaze in order to
find its way from the bottom left to the
piece of cheese
puzzle
[Music]
foreign
as shown
in other words the mosque can find more
than one solutions
[Music]
let's consider another problem the most
problem noticeable problems
problems that are conducted much already
consider the sequence of numbers below
[Music]
intelligence world
foreign
[Music]
travel
foreign
artificial intelligence
m
so
[Music]
foreign
take the